[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Saturday Night Fever, Tony Manero and his friends go dancing in order to escape from the harsh reality of life. What is the name of the disco club they visit every Saturday night?", "correct_answer": "2001 Odyssey", "incorrect_answers": ["Elefas", "Thriller", "Boogie Wonderland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Norman Bates is a popular book and film villain. Whose personality does he assume as a result from a dissociative identity disorder?", "correct_answer": "His mothers", "incorrect_answers": ["His dead wifes", "Marilyn Monroes", "Sigmund Freuds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the last veteran of the American Civil War die?", "correct_answer": "1958", "incorrect_answers": ["1944", "1949", "1936"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the late 1980s which television station did Rosie ODonnell work for?", "correct_answer": "VH1", "incorrect_answers": ["CBS", "MTV", "ABC"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the American Civil War, what were the southern US states referred to as?", "correct_answer": "Confederacy", "incorrect_answers": ["Republicans", "Democrats", "Union"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning actor stars in the 1988 comedy movie Big?", "correct_answer": "Tom Hanks", "incorrect_answers": ["Robin Williams", "Dustin Hoffman", "Sean Penn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Polonium?", "correct_answer": "Po", "incorrect_answers": ["Pl", "Pn", "P"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The King Cobra feeds almost exclusively on other snakes, even toxic ones.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Louis Armstrong sings this great, old, romantic song on the Sleepless in Seattle soundtrack.", "correct_answer": "A Kiss to Build a Dream On", "incorrect_answers": ["Saint Louis Blues", "When Its Sleepy Time, Down South", "My Heart Is Yours Forever"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Utah, wine used in wine tasting cannot be swallowed.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Bodhi tree, located near Bodh Gaya in India, is of great importance to the followers of Buddhism, because it is considered to be related to the spiritual teacher, Buddha, in what way?", "correct_answer": "Buddha found enlightenment under this tree.", "incorrect_answers": ["Buddha died under this tree.", "God Vishnu spoke to him for the first time under this tree.", "It is Buddhas birth place."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The history of EU began on 25th of March 1957 when the European Economic Community was formed. What is the founding act called?", "correct_answer": "Treaty of Rome", "incorrect_answers": ["Treaty of Paris", "Schengen Agreement", "Schuman Declaration"]}]